[{"answer": "It's just been electric all day, Piers.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "How would you describe the mood there?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, this is -- this is our understanding at the moment.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Do we have a clearer picture?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Extraordinary.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What have I done to you?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Dan, for now, thank you very much.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Was he really hit by crossfire as they tried to take him to the hospital as the NTC claims, or was this a mob out of control and someone decided to execute him on the spot?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "I care about one thing.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "And I guess the other question I'd ask you is, do you care?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Well, the future for Libya is going to very bright.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "How do you see the future for Libya mapping out?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "No, I'm not talking about government.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "And Your Highness, do you hope to have a role yourself in any future Libyan government?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, oil going to be -- going to be developed, bring back to 1.6 to 2 million barrels a day.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "What happens about oil now?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "It is an understatement if I tell you that -- I can't even describe.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "When you saw the video footage, how did you feel?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I was in my office when we first heard the news.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Where were you when you heard the news?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly think we should be talking to the transitional national council as it moves to establish a government in Libya.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "What is your view of that?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "This is a huge milestone.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "Where does this rank in terms of significance, the demise of Moammar Gadhafi, do you think?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "There is.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "You know the scenario there, isn't there, about how he met his maker?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, I think this is historic, and I don't think it's going to be a precedent that is going to lead us to move into Syria or other places.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Do you think that we're seeing a whole sea change here in terms of American foreign policy?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, I have a lot of friends who are pretty wary.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "What do you think will happen in Libya in the short to middle term?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, the first thought was, this was an erratic mysterious who was murderous and defiant to the end.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "What were your thoughts today when you heard that he's finally gone?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting you say that, I've got someone you now well, General Mark Kimmitt, with me.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "This was a triumph for the moment, the question now is, can we build on that triumph and help the Libyans become what they can become?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, I think, first of all, Dan Rather was precise in his forecast and I very much associate myself with those comments as well.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, it doesn't concern me.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Or does that in itself concern you?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "It's absolutely extraordinary.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Isn't this extraordinary what is going on?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, the NTC has, I think, made great strides since the uprising started in February.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Are they equipped, do you think, the NTC, to build a new government?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "I think the divisions that we're seeing in Libya and the fault lines that I just mentioned a minute ago do make it difficult, I think, to really go very quickly, that is at least in a kind of democratic direction, the way that we in the west would like to see.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Is it harder when you have so many different tribal elements?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, I think everyone in the Gadhafi regime that was involved with terrorist attacks against America should be held accountable.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, a month ago, I had met with the current Libyan president -- President Jalil, who pledged to me that he and his regime wanted to bring Gadhafi to justice, not only for the murder of -- of John and other innocent civilians, but also for the murder of his people.", "docId": "111020pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Or are you happy that he was possibly executed in fairly brutal fashion by the rebels?", "qSentId": 369}]